Office of Alumni Relations Records UA011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Secretary of Alumni Assocation, Fred Nickless, 1950 -- 1987; 1967 -- 1984; UA011.009; 8.9 Linear Feet
  - Chrono file, 1974 -- 1987; UA011.009.060.00008 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1974; UA011.009.060.00009 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1974; UA011.009.060.00010 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1974; UA011.009.060.00011 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1975; UA011.009.060.00012 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1975; UA011.009.060.00013 (Box 60)
  - Chrono file, 1975; UA011.009.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1975; UA011.009.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1975 -- 1976; UA011.009.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1976; UA011.009.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1976; UA011.009.061.00005 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1976; UA011.009.061.00006 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1976; UA011.009.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1977; UA011.009.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1977; UA011.009.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - Chrono file, 1977; UA011.009.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - Chronological file, 1977; UA011.009.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - Chronological file, 1978; UA011.009.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Chronological file, 1978; UA011.009.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Chrono file, 1978; UA011.009.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Chrono file, 1978; UA011.009.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - Chrono file, 1978 -- 1979; UA011.009.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - Chronological file, 1979; UA011.009.062.00006 (Box 62)
    Also contains letter found on Reading Room shelves from "Peter" regarding his receipt of a 1979 Distinguished Service Award. Letter is in back of folder, dated March 5, 1979. On URI stationary.
  - Chrono file, 1979; UA011.009.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Chrono file, 1979; UA011.009.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - Chrono file, 1979 -- 1980; UA011.009.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Chrono file, 1980; UA011.009.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1980; UA011.009.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1980; UA011.009.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1981; UA011.009.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1981; UA011.009.063.00005 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1981; UA011.009.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1981 -- 1982; UA011.009.063.00007 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1982; UA011.009.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1982; UA011.009.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1983; UA011.009.063.00010 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1983; UA011.009.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - Chrono file, 1982 -- 1983; UA011.009.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Chrono file, 1983 -- 1984; UA011.009.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Chrono file, 1984; UA011.009.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Sheetz correspondence, 1969; UA011.009.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1968 -- 1970; UA011.009.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1969 -- 1970; UA011.009.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1970 -- 1971; UA011.009.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1971; UA011.009.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1971 -- 1972; UA011.009.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1972 -- 1973; UA011.009.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1973; UA011.009.064.00011 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1973 -- 1974; UA011.009.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1975; UA011.009.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - Staff communications, 1975; UA011.009.064.00014 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1958 -- 1961; UA011.009.064.00015 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick corerspondence, 1961 -- 1962; UA011.009.064.00016 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1962; UA011.009.064.00017 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1958 -- 1962; UA011.009.064.00018 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1958 -- 1963; UA011.009.064.00019 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1963 -- 1964; UA011.009.064.00020 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1964 -- 1965; UA011.009.064.00021 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1964 -- 1966; UA011.009.064.00022 (Box 64)
  - Tredinnick correspondence, 1966 -- 1967; UA011.009.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - Deaths reported, 1976; UA011.009.065.00002 (Box 65)
    This file is restricted.
  - Handbooks, 1957 -- 1966; UA011.009.065.00003 (Box 65)
  - Alumni house, photographs, various floors and rooms, 1977; UA011.009.065.00004 (Box 65)
    Photographs found uncataloged in the stacks in the winter of 2009.
- Secretary of Alumni Assocation, Joseph W. Morton, 1924 -- 1959; UA011.010; 0.25 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence and photographs from Joseph W. Morton.
  - Correspondence Files, 1930 -- 1959; UA011.010.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - Photographs, 1924 -- 1958; UA011.010.066.00002 (Box 66)
  - 30th Anniversary Photographs, 1954; UA011.010.066.00003 (Box 66)
    Included original photograph removed from frame.
- 2017 accessions, circa 1927 -- 2010; UA011.011; 1 Reels; 4 Photographic Prints; 1.6 Linear Feet; 8 Digital Object(s) 8 digital objects containing 362 files
  This series is open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the Office of Alumni Relations, 2017, accession UA-2018-014.
  This series is arranged in received order.
  This series contains an alumni scrapbook, photographs of Tufts graduating classes, event brochures, event photographs, audio reels and cassettes, and powerpoints of presentations.
  - Alumni Day and Commencement audio reel, June 1965; UA011.011.068; 1 Reels (Box 68)
  - Tufts and Jackson class photograph, 1934; UA011.011.069; 1 Photographic Prints 1 oversize photograph (Frame 69)
  - Tufts and Jackson class photograph, 1936; UA011.011.070; 1 Photographic Prints 1 oversize photograph (Frame 70)
  - Tufts and Jackson class photograph, 1940; UA011.011.071; 1 Photographic Prints 1 oversize photograph (Frame 71)
  - Tufts and Jackson class photograph, 1941; UA011.011.072; 1 Photographic Prints 1 oversize photograph (Frame 72)
  - Connecticut Tufts Club scrapbook, circa 1927 -- 1967; UA011.011.073; .4 Linear Feet 1 oversize box (Box 73)
    Custodial History
    Donated to the Office of Alumni Relations in memory of of Tufts alumnus and volunteer Chapter Leader Robert Bartlett Hempstead A61 by his wife Sally Hempstead of Wethersfield, Connecticut.
  - Alumni Weekend brochures, 1959 -- 1972; UA011.011.074.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Alumni Weekend brochures, 1972 -- 1984; UA011.011.074.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Alumni Weekend brochures, 1985 -- 1995; UA011.011.074.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Alumni Weekend brochures, 1996 -- 2014; UA011.011.074.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Nantucket event photographs, circa 1999; UA011.011.074.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Class of 1954 25th Reunion photograph, 1979; UA011.011.074.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Bedford Village photographs, 2002; UA011.011.074.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Jacksonville and Sarasota event photographs, 2002; UA011.011.074.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Reunions photographs, circa 1998 -- 2005; UA011.011.074.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Homecoming brochures, 1990 -- 2002; UA011.011.074.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Tuftonia's Day, 1992 -- 1994; UA011.011.074.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Jackson College materials, 1942 -- 1959; UA011.011.074.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
    This file includes a Senior Banquet brouchure (1942), a directory (1956-1957), and the Junior Poetry Anthology (1959).
  - Threshold of Greatness Campaign brochures, circa 1960; UA011.011.074.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Alumni Association Speaker Series notes, 2003 -- 2007; UA011.011.074.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous notes and minutes, 2007 -- 2010; UA011.011.074.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Gregory Maguire in New York City cassette, 2008; UA011.011.074.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 74)
  - Cape Cod Alumni Trip, Dean Norris, 2005; UA011.011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Florida Alumni Trip, Dean Norris, 2005; UA011.011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Gregory Maguire Event photographs, 2008; UA011.011.00003; 224 Digital Object(s)
  - NM Tufts Reunion Pictures, 2005; UA011.011.00004; 51 Digital Object(s)
  - Martha's Vineyard Pictures, 2004; UA011.011.00005; 26 Digital Object(s)
  - Alumni Speaker Series: Eileen Kennedy, 2004; UA011.011.00006; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Provost in DC Photographs, 2004; UA011.011.00007; 32 Digital Object(s)
  - Law Day Photographs, 2004; UA011.011.00008; 26 Digital Object(s)
- 2018 accessions, circa 1917 -- 1989; UA011.012; .25 Linear Feet
  This series contains four photographs: East Hall, 1917; Military Company, 1917; drawing of Alumni House, undated; untitled and undated photograph of Tufts event, circa 1980s.
  This series is arranged in order of accession.
  - Photographs, circa 1917 -- 1989; UA011.012.075; .25 Linear Feet (Box 75)
    Transferred by the Office of Alumni Relations, 2018, accession UA-2019-019.
    This file contains four photographs: East Hall, 1917; Military Company, 1917; drawing of Alumni House, undated; untitled and undated photograph of Tufts event, circa 1980s.
- 2019 accessions, 1895 -- 1896; UA011.013; .2 Linear Feet
  This series contains a photograph of the Tufts College Glee, Guitar, and Mandolin Clubs from 1895-1896.
  - Tufts College Glee, Guitar, and Mandolin Clubs photograph, 1895 -- 1896; UA011.013.076; .2 Linear Feet (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 5)
    Transferred by the Office of Alumni Relations, 2019, accession UA-2019-061.
- Additional accessions, 1913 -- 2008; UA011.014
  - Tufts Criterion photos of alumni, 1980 -- 1993; UA011-017 (Box 1)
  - Advancement committee; Black history; oral history; time capsule letters; framed items, 1924 -- 2007; UA011-016 (Box 2)
  - Fred Nickless, Elephant Statues, UA011-008 (Box 3)
  - Two Tufts plates, 1957; Tufts handbook, 1913-1914, 1913 -- 1957; UA011-005 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Magazine photo files, UA011-004 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Magazine photo files, UA011-003 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Magazine photo files, UA011-002 (Box 7)
  - Pamphlets and brochures and notepad, 1960 -- 2008; UA011-001 (Box 8)
- 2020 accessions, 2019; UA011.000544; 0.1 Linear Feet
  Transferred by the Office of Alumni Relations, 2020, UA-2020-055.
  This series contains two copies of the Class of 1969 50th Anniversary Yearbook.
  - Class of 1969 50th Reunion Yearbook, 2019; UA011.000545 (Box 74, Folder 17)